Finding Aid for Finding Aid for School of Music (University of Michigan) Records, 1880-2010.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Faculty Records
  - Faculty File
    Faculty Files document both administrative correspondence with faculty and the professional activities of faculty. They include information regarding salaries, teaching responsibilities, courses taught, etc. Files are present for both current and retired faculty, having started as early as 1934. Files for adjunct professors are also included.
    Deceased Faculty Files include the same kinds of documents.
    - Alcantra, Theo (1965-1984) (Box 9)
    - Alexius, Carl (1962-1986) (Box 9)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2016 ]
    - Allen, Nancy (1984-1985) (Box 9)
    - Altman, Robert (Box 9)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2035 ]
    - Anderson, Lucille (Box 9)
    - Aronson, Arnold (1986-1991) (Box 9)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2021 ]
    - Atamian, Dickran (1991-1996) (Box 9)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2026 ]
    - Ballard, Gregory (1980-1993) (Box 9)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2023 ]
    - Barfield, Sencer (1994-1995) (Box 9)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2025 ]
    - Barkin, Elaine (1970-1974) (Box 9)
    - Barone, Clement (Box 9)
    - Bartholomew, Lynne B. (Box 9)
    - Bashour, Frederick J. (1974-1977) (Box 9)
    - Bassett, L. (1952-1992) (Box 9)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2022 ]
    - Becher, Eric A. (1980-1989) (Box 9)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2019 ]
    - Bender, Jack (1979-1987) (Box 9)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2017 ]
    - Benjamin, William E. (1972-1982) (Box 9)
    - Berg, James (1968-1971) (Box 9)
    - Bergman, Elizabeth (1979-1988) (Box 9)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2018 ]
    - Beudert, Peter M. (1987) (Box 9)
    - Bilik, Jerry (1962-1977) (Box 9)
    - Billings, Alan (Box 9)
    - Boardman, Eunice (Fall 1998) (Box 9)
    - Bossart, Eugene (1954-1984) (Box 9)
    - Boyette, Patricia (1986-1988) (Box 9)
    - Brater, Enoch (1975- ) (Box 9)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2030 ]
    - Bridges, Wallace A. (1996) (Box 9)
    - Britton, A. (1949-1984) (Box 10)
    - Broening, Benjamin (Box 10)
    - Brown, John Russell (1987-1997) 2 Folders (Box 10)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2027 ]
    - Brown, Rae Linda (1986-1989) (Box 10)
    - Browne, Richmond (1968-1995) (Box 10)
    - Bruhn, Siglind (1993-1995) (Box 10)
    - Buyse, Leone (1994-1994) (Box 10)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2024 ]
    - Bryan, Keith (1964-1994) (Box 10)
    - Burt, George J. (1967-1985) (Box 10)
    - Cardenes, Andres J. (1987-1989) (Box 10)
    - Cates, Millard Hyle (1958-1967) (Box 10)
    - Cavender, George (1979-1990), 2 folders (Box 10)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2020 ]
    - Chang, Shirley (1996-1997) (Box 10)
    - Chudacoff, Edward M. (1954-1996) (Box 10)
    - Clark, Janice (1958) (Box 10)
    - Clark, Robert C. (1964-1981) (Box 10)
    - Clark, Ruth D. (1957-1983) (Box 10)
    - Cleaver, Gerald (1994-2000) (Box 10)
    - Clough, John L. (1970-1981) (Box 11)
    - Cochran, Mary (1996-1997) (Box 11)
    - Cohen, Albert (1960-1970) (Box 11)
    - Cole, Mary (1998) (Box 11)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2028 ]
    - Coleman, Clarence (1988) (Box 11)
    - Conley, Joyce K. (1978-1981) (Box 11)
    - Cooper, Kenneth (1955-1968) (Box 11)
    - Cooper, Lewis Hugh (1945-1990) (Box 11)
    - Cornett, Stanley (1983-1987) (Box 11)
    - Crawford, David E. (1967-2001) (Box 11)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2031 ]
    - Crow, Laura (1987- ) (Box 11)
    - Curtis-Smith, Curtis (1996- ) (Box 11)
    - Daub, Peggy (Box 11)
    - Delzell, Judith K. (1981-1985) (Box 11)
    - De Turk, William (1981-1987) (Box 11)
    - Divorak, Thomas L. (1975-1978) (Box 11)
    - de los Cobos, Sergio (Box 11)
    - DuBois, Wendi A. 1998-1999 (Box 11)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2029 ]
    - Duso, Lorraine (Box 11)
    - Edel, Oliver (1943-1976) (Box 11)
    - Elliker, Calvin (1993-2001) (Box 11)
    - Embree, Vera (1968-1987) (Box 11)
    - Esposito, Mark (1988) (Box 11)
    - Eysselinck, Walter (1980-1988) (Box 11)
    - Ferran, Peter (1967-1994) (Box 11)
    - Fischer, Penny (1990-1991) (Box 11)
    - Fisher, Charles Raymond (1953-1991) (Box 11)
    - Flower, J. (Box 11)
    - Froseth, James (1971-2000) (Box 12)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2030 ]
    - Fujiwara, Hamao (Box 12)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2035 ]
    - Gardner, Patrick G. (1981-1990) (Box 12)
    - Ghitalia, Armando (1979-1994) (Box 12)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2024 ]
    - Gillian, Jeffrey (1989-1990) (Box 12)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2020 ]
    - Grammatico, Renee (1994-1995) (Box 12)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2025 ]
    - Greer, Frances (1954-1972) (Box 12)
    - Greer, Lowell David (1998) (Box 12)
    - Gregory, David D. (1984-1993) (Box 12)
    - Grogan, Jeffrey (1995-1996) (Box 12)
    - Glocke, Dennis R. (1990-1996) (Box 12)
    - Good, Alan (1994-1995) (Box 12)
    - Guinn, Leslie (Box 12)
    - Halstead, Clarabel Baird (1990) (Box 12)
    - Hardie, Graham H. (1970-1975) (Box 12)
    - Hatten, Robert S. (1982-1989) (Box 12)
    - Haugh, Harold Albert (1948-1976) (Box 12)
    - Haywood, Lorna (Box 12)
    - Hilbish, Thomas (1964-1988) (Box 12)
    - Hitchcock, H. Wiley (1950-1962) (Box 12)
    - Hodkinson, Sydney P. (1969-1973)] (Box 12)
    - Hurst, Lawrence (1963-1986) 2 Folders (Box 12)
    - Jackson, Charles A. (1987-1994) (Box 12)
    - Jacobi, Roger E. (1960-1979) 2 Folders (Box 13)
    - Jelinek, Jerome (1961-1996) (Box 13)
    - Johnson, Ken (Ken Leigh Rogers stage name) Winter 1998 (Box 13)
    - Kalt, Percy G. (1973-1975) (Box 13)
    - Kennedy, Bryan (Box 13)
    - Klein, Alex (Box 13)
    - Klinger, Joseph (1996-1997) (Box 13)
    - Knopf, Robert (Box 13)
    - Krachmalnick, Jacob M. (1978-1990) (Box 13)
    - Kraus, Elizabeth Mosher (1970-1979) (Box 13)
    - Krieger, Mitchell (1986-1990) (Box 13)
    - Ladd, R. Hudson (1971-1981) (Box 13)
    - LeBlanc, Robert (1995-1996) (Box 13)
    - Lettvin, Theodore (1977-1987) (Box 13)
    - Levin, David (Box 13)
    - Lee, Grace (Box 13)
    - Lehman, Paul and Ruth (1975-1997) (Box 13)
    - Lelchuk, Nina (Fall 1998) (Box 13)
    - Lerdahl, Fred (Box 13)
    - Lesenger, Jay (1985-1989) (Box 13)
    - Lewis, Gary Joe (1990-1991) (Box 13)
    - Lewis, Ralph (1965-1998) (Box 13)
    - Likova-Baca, Eva (1966-1983) (Box 13)
    - Luscombe, Robert H. (1968-1973) (Box 13)
    - Lykes, Karen (1989-1990) (Box 13)
    - Major, Elizabeth (Box 14)
    - Malm, William (1960-1994) (Box 14)
    - MaGee, Jeffrey (1993-1997) (Box 14)
    - Manion, Elizabeth B. (1966-1968) (Box 14)
    - Marsh, Lawrence B. (1976-1981) (Box 14)
    - Matheke, Susan (1979-1983) (Box 14)
    - Mayer, Uri (1974-1976) (Box 14)
    - McCollum, John (1962-1988) (Box 14)
    - McDaniel, Lorna (1991-1992) (Box 14)
    - McInnes, Donald (1982-1985) (Box 14)
    - McIntosh, Julian & Vera (1984-1996) (Box 14)
    - McMurray, Allan R. (1976-1978) (Box 14)
    - McDeek, Gwynn S. (1968-1981) (Box 14)
    - McTerry, Harry James (1973-1975) (Box 14)
    - Meier, Gustav (1975-1995) (Box 14)
    - Mendeloff, Katherine (Box 14)
    - Milanov, Rossen (Box 14)
    - Miller, Richard Dean (1957-1963) (Box 14)
    - Mischakoff, Matthew (1991-1992) (Box 14)
    - Mohler, John (1962-1994) (Box 14)
    - Monson, Dale E. (1982-1991) (Box 14)
    - Monson, Ingrid (1995-1996) (Box 14)
    - Monforte, John (Box 14)
    - Moore, Earl V. (1945-1988) (Box 14)
    - Mountain, Michelle (Box 15)
    - Munson, Paul A. (1996-1997) (Box 15)
    - Nadon-Gabrion, Catherine A. (1977) (Box 15)
    - Nel, Anton (1992-2000) (Box 15)
    - Nelson, Craig Richard (Box 15)
    - Nelson, Geneva (1946-1974) (Box 15)
    - Newby, Stephen (Box 15)
    - Nibley, Reid (1964-1969) (Box 15)
    - Nightingale, Benedict (1986-1990) (Box 15)
    - Noehren, Robert (1949-1976) (Box 15)
    - O'Brien-Pedersen, Julianne (Box 15)
    - Ornelas, Reuben (Box 15)
    - Osmond, Stephen (1977-1980) (Box 15)
    - Pacha, Melinda (1997-1998) (Box 15)
    - Patterson, Willis (1968-2000) (Box 15)
    - Pikcut, Kurt and Margot (1980) (Box 15)
    - Piltzecker, Ted (1977) (Box 15)
    - Polot, Barton L. (Box 15)
    - Potter, Wendy Ann (1997-1998) (Box 15)
    - Powers, Katherine (Box 15)
    - Rabbio, Salvatore (1988-1998) (Box 15)
    - Rabin, Ronald J. (1997-1998) (Box 15)
    - Rachleff, Larry (1983-1986) (Box 15)
    - Rehding, Alexander (2000-2003) (Box 15)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2033 ]
    - Revelli, William D. (1935-1994) (Box 16)
    - Reynolds, H. Robert (Box 16)
    - Ricci, Ruggiero (1982-1988) (Box 16)
    - Richter, Glenn A. (1979-1980) (Box 16)
    - Rinaldi, Beverley (1980-1984) (Box 16)
    - Roberts, Wilfred (1998) (Box 16)
    - Rosenberg, Richard (1987-1990) (Box 16)
    - Ross, Daniel F. (1998) (Box 16)
    - Rosseels, Gustave (1957-1979) (Box 16)
    - Roth, Ari (1989) (Box 16)
    - Rothstein, William (1983-1992) (Box 16)
    - Rouse, Christopher C. (1978-1979) (Box 16)
    - Ruehr, Elena (Box 16)
    - Sandor, Gyorgy (1961-1982) (Box 16)
    - Sankey, Stuart (Box 16)
    - Saxton, Keith (Box 16)
    - Schleicher, Donald John (1986-1995) (Box 16)
    - Schleuter, Stanley (Box 16)
    - Sellheim, Eckhart (1983-1989) (Box 16)
    - Sedatole, Kevin (1996-1997) (Box 16)
    - Shifrin, David A. (1976-1893) (Box 16)
    - Siebert, John (1997-1998) (Box 16)
    - Simmons, Renee (1994-1995) (Box 16)
    - Sisman, Elaine R. (1976-1982) (Box 16)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2082 ]
    - Smith, Dennis (1980-2000) (Box 16)
    - Smith, Fenwick (1997-1998) (Box 16)
    - Smith, Joanne (1983- ) (Box 16)
    - Smith, Matthew (Box 16)
    - Soledade, Augusto (Box 16)
    - Solow, Jeffrey (1984-1989) (Box 17)
    - Spencer, Julie (1994-1995) (Box 17)
    - Spitzer, John (1984-1987) (Box 17)
    - Spriggs, Linda (1987-1995) (Box 17)
    - St. Clair, Carl (1978-1986) (Box 17)
    - Standifer, James A. 3 Folders (Box 17)
    - Stillings, Frank (1953-1962) (Box 17)
    - Stout, Louis (1961-1989) (Box 17)
    - Sutherland, David A. (1972-1988) (Box 17)
    - Sutherland, Enid D. (1974-1991) (Box 17)
    - Swanson, Bessie R. (1966-1973) (Box 17)
    - Tai, Shih-Ting C. (2000-2001) (Box 17)
    - Tan, Victor En Yu (1990-1997) (Box 17)
    - Tapia, James (Box 17)
    - Teeple, Scott A. (Box 17)
    - Thorne, Nicholas (1986-1988) (Box 17)
    - Torchinsky, Abe (1972-1990) (Box 17)
    - Udon, Nancy L. (1986-1990) (Box 17)
    - Vander Weg, John Dean (Box 18)
    - Ventura, Brian (Box 18)
    - Wagner, Corbin (1996-2000) (Box 18)
    - Walsh, Martin (1993-1996) (Box 18)
    - Walton, Joan (Box 18)
    - Walwyn, Karen (1994- ) (Box 18)
    - Watkins, Howard (1989-1994) (Box 18)
    - Watkins, Glenn (1961-1996) (Box 18)
    - Watts, Andre (Box 18)
    - Weckler, Ellen R. (1974-1994) (Box 18)
    - Weckstrom, Virginia M. (1989-1990) (Box 18)
    - Weisfeld, Zelma H. (1984-1990) (Box 18)
    - Whitaker, Rodney (1996-1997) (Box 18)
    - Wicks, Camilla (1984-1988) (Box 18)
    - Widaryanto, F.X. (1995-1996) (Box 18)
    - Williams, Robert (Winter 1998) (Box 18)
    - Wilson, Eric (1999-2000) (Box 18)
    - Wilson, George Balch (1958-1994) (Box 18)
    - Winn, James A. (1996-1998) (Box 18)
    - Withrow, Norval (1970-1974) (Box 18)
    - Workman, Reggie (1994-1996) (Box 18)
    - Workman, Maya (1995-2000) (Box 18)
    - Xiao, Hong-Mei (1997-1999) (Box 18)
  - Deceased Faculty Files
    - Adamson, Quin 1975-1985 (d. 1991) (Box 19)
    - Albright, William H. 1970-1998 (d. 1998) (Box 19)
    - Bird, Gary 1994-2000 (d. 2000) (Box 19)
    - Blatt, J. 1952-1976 (d. 1999) (Box 19)
    - Bundra, Francis D. 1965-1992 (Box 19)
    - Dalley, Orien 1950-1971 (d. 1999) (Box 19)
    - Dexter, Benning 1949-1985 (d. 1996) (Box 19)
    - Finney, Ross Lee 1947-1974 (Box 19)
    - Gabrion, Charles J. 1968-1980 (d. 1994) (Box 19)
    - Giles, Sidney (d. 1985) (Box 19)
    - Hartshorn, William C. (d. 1974) (Box 19)
    - Hilgenberg, Katherine E. 1968-1986 (d. 1988) (Box 19)
    - Hood, Marguerite 1942-1973 (Box 19)
    - Hord, Robert 1955-1984 (d. 1990) (Box 19)
    - Hunt, Marian Owen 1946-1978 (Box 19)
    - Janes, Betty Jean 1994-1995 (Box 19)
    - Kern, Alice M. 1950-1976 (d. 1993) (Box 19)
    - Klein, Maynard 1948-1977 (d. 1990) (Box 19)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2077 ]
    - Kollen, John Lloyd 1934-1982 (d. 1982) (Box 19)
    - Lewis, Thelma B. 1929-1982 (d. 1982) (Box 19)
    - Libby, Dennis A. (d. 1990) (Box 19)
    - Lucone, Albert 1943-1984 (d. 1984) (Box 19)
    - Lillya, Clifford P. 1937-1980 (d. 1998) (Box 19)
    - Mayes, Samuel 1975-1985 (d. 1990) (Box 19)
    - McGeoch, Glenn (d. 1983) (Box 19)
    - Mueller, Florian (d. 1983) (Box 19)
    - Power, Eugene B. (Box 20)
    - Price, Percival (d. 1985) (Box 20)
    - Owen, Charles E. 1972-1983 (d. 1985) (Box 20)
    - Price, Frank 1939-1972 (d. 1985) (Box 20)
    - Reyes, Angel (d. 1988) (Box 20)
    - Ross, Gilbert (d. 1993) (Box 20)
    - Salmon, James 1954-1972 (d. 1989) (Box 20)
    - Smith, Glenn P. 1950-1981 (Box 20)
    - Thompson, Clyde (d. 1985) (Box 20)
    - Troth, Eugene 1953-1971 (d. 1991) (Box 20)
    - Vroman, Clyde (d. 1981) (Box 20)
    - Wallace, James B. (d. 1983) (Box 20)
    - Wardrop, Lare 1943-1975 (d. 1979) (Box 20)
    - Warner, Robert (d. 1986) (Box 20)
    - Weechlein, William (d. 1988) (Box 20)
    - Whitmire, Anthony J. (d. 1975) (Box 20)
  - Promotion Files
    Promotion Files pertain to promotion reviews for faculty that both did and did not receive promotions. They include letters of recommendation, curriculum vitae, external and internal reviews, and final decisions. They span from 1980-2000.
    - 1980-1992, 36 folders (Box 21)
      [PR RESTRICTED for 30 years from date of creation]
    - 1982-1999, 33 folders (Box 22)
    - 1999-2000 (13 Folders (Box 23)
  - Sabbatical Requests
    Sabbatical Requests contain the actual request forms, description of projects to be completed, and correspondence while on sabbatical. These span from 1978-1998.
    - 1978-1982 (Box 23)
    - 1983-1995 (Box 23)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 23)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 23)
    - 1987-1989 (Box 23)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 23)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 23)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 23)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 23)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 23)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 23)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 23)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 23)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 23)
  - Faculty Activities Reports
    Faculty Activity Reports document the activities of the faculty within each individual department of the School of Music for a given year. The years 1998 and 1999 are included in the collection.
    - 1998
      - Composition (Box 24)
      - Conducting (Box 24)
      - Dance (Box 24)
      - Jazz Studies (Box 24)
      - Keyboard Studies (Box 24)
      - Media/Music Technology (Box 24)
      - Music Education (Box 24)
      - Musicology (Box 24)
      - Music Theory (Box 24)
      - Musical Theatre (Box 24)
      - Organ (Box 24)
      - Strings (Box 24)
      - Theatre (Box 24)
      - Voice (Box 24)
      - Winds (Box 24)
    - 1999
      - Composition (Box 24)
      - Conducting (Box 24)
      - Dance (Box 24)
      - Jazz Studies (Box 24)
      - Media/Music Technology (Box 24)
      - Music Education (Box 24)
      - Musicology (Box 24)
      - Music Theory (Box 24)
      - Musical Theatre (Box 24)
      - Organ (Box 24)
      - Piano (Box 24)
      - Strings (Box 24)
      - Theatre (Box 24)
      - Voice (Box 24)
      - Winds (Box 24)
- Dean Files
  - Paul Boylan
    Dean Boylan's Files span the years from the late 1960s to 2000. They include correspondence, curriculum vitae, Executive Committee Records, Speeches and conference information.
    - Advisory Council (Box 30)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1 2025 ]
    - Correspondence
      - 1968-1993 (Box 30)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 30)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 30)
    - Curriculum Vitae (Box 30)
    - Executive Committee
      - 1995-1996 (Box 30)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 30)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 31)
    - Museum of Art Executive Committee (Box 31)
    - Second International Conference of Music/Cognition at UCLA (Box 31)
    - Speeches (Box 31)
- Donor Files
  Donor Files include correspondence, biographical information and acknowledgment of donations from the late 1980s and early 1990s.
  - Capital Campaign Kickoff Info September 1992 (Box 31)
  - Flint, Annette S. (Box 31)
  - Frolich, Edward (Box 31)
  - Frye, Mary Caroline (Box 31)
  - Gomick, Pauline and Alan (Box 31)
  - Heyde, Dr. and Mrs. John (Box 31)
  - Istock, Judith and Verne (Box 31)
  - Rossi, Dominic and Evelyn (Box 31)
  - Jones, Ernest A. (Box 31)
  - Goodman, Julia (Box 31)
  - Kelly, Gene (Box 31)
  - Light, Christopher (Son of Mary Meader) (Box 31)
  - Madonna (Box 31)
  - McKee, Robert (Box 31)
  - McIntosh, Mildred (Box 31)
  - Meader, Edwin (Box 31)
  - Moore, Vincent (Box 31)
  - Music's Capital Campaign 1991-1992 (Box 31)
  - Ormandy, Eugene (Box 31)
  - Rogel, Richard and Susan (Box 31)
  - Lang, Michael (Box 31)
  - Rumelhart, Judith Dow (Box 31)
  - Rich, John (Box 31)
  - Robertson, Sanford (Box 31)
  - Schnitzer, Robert C. (Box 31)
  - Sperry, Ann (Box 31)
  - Stephanz, Kenneth (Box 31)
  - Stranahan, Betsy (Box 31)
  - University’s Capital Campaign (Box 31)
  - Weiser, Ronald and Eileen (Mckinley Foundation, 1988) (Box 31)
  - Wu, Clyde and Helen (Box 31)
  - Young, Shirley (Box 31)
- Executive Committee 1972-1999
  Executive Committee records include abstracts and minutes from meetings from 1972 to 1999.
  - Abstracts
    - 1972-1982 (Box 32)
    - 1983-1987 (Box 32)
    - 1988-1999 (Box 32)
  - Minutes
    - 1987-1988 (Box 32)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 32)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 32)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 32)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 32)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 32)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 32)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 32)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 32)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 32)
  - Nominations
    - Information (Box 32)
    - Communications (Box 32)
- Department of Theatre and Drama
  Department of Theatre and Drama includes correspondence from the late 1988-1999, budget information, personnel files, etc.
  - Big Ten Theatre Administrators Conference (4/28/1990) (Box 33)
  - BFA in Theatre (Box 33)
  - Budget Information (Box 33)
  - Chair's Correspondence
    - 1990-1991 (Box 33)
    - 1991-1993 (Box 33)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 33)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 33)
  - Chair Search (Box 33)
  - Personnel (Box 33)
  - Professional Theatre Program (Box 33)
  - Theatre Department 1983 (Box 33)
  - Theatre Department 1984 (Box 33)
  - Theatre Transfer File 1983 (Box 33)
  - Correspondence
    - 1997-1998 (Box 33)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 33)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 33)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 33)
- Archived Website
  The Archived Website series (2002-2008, 2.13 GB; 2010-[ONGOING]) documents the academic programs, accomplishments, resources, events, and people at the School of Music, Theatre & Dance. Content includes important news and announcements, publications (such as newsletters and student handbooks), and information about departments, admissions, curriculum, degree requirements, performances, faculty, alumni relations, special youth and adult programs, and the overall mission of the School. The series is arranged chronologically and includes content captured by the Internet Archive starting in 1996 as well as captures provided by Bentley Library archivists in 2002, 2003, 2006 and ca. 2008. Starting in 2010, this archived website will be captured on a regular, ongoing basis as part of the University of Michigan Web Archives, hosted at http://webarchives.cdlib.org/a/universityofmichigan/
  - School of Music, Theatre & Dance
    - 1996-[ONGOING]
      (These versions were preserved by the Internet Archive and are made available through its Wayback Machine. The Bentley Historical Library is not involved in the collection or maintenance of this material.)
    - May 15, 2002, .ZIP file
    - May 22, 2003, .ZIP file
    - February 23, 2006, .ZIP file
    - 2008, .ZIP file
    - 2010-[ONGOING]
  - Related Resources: Curricula, Degree Requirements, Research, Events, etc.
    - 2010-[ONGOING]